是啊兄弟
Yeah man
我们又回到了夜店
So we back in the club
大家的身体一起左右摇摆起来
Get that bodies rockin from side to side (side to side)
感谢上帝又到了周末
Thank God the week is done
我感觉像是僵尸重获新生
I feel like a zombie gone back to life (back to life)
举起双手
Hands up
瞬间大家都举起的双手
and suddenly we all got our hands up
身体似乎不再受控制
No control of my body
以前我见过你么
Ain't I seen you before
我认为我记得
I think I remember those
你的眼神...
eyes,eyes,eyes(ei...)
宝贝,因为今晚
Cause baby tonight
DJ让我们再次相爱
The DJ got us falling in love again
耶宝贝,今晚
Yeah, baby tonight
DJ让我们再次相爱
The DJ got us falling in love again
那就跳舞,就好像
So dance, dance, like it's the last
今晚是生命中的最后一晚
last night of your life, life
得让你进入正轨
Gonna get you right
宝贝,因为今晚
Cause baby tonight
DJ让我们再次相爱
The DJ got us falling in love again
不停的像这样喝着酒
Keep downing drinks like this
我说的不是明天,而是现在
Not tomorrow that just right now
现在...
now, now, now, now, now, now
让我们把屋顶点燃
Gonna set the roof on fire
把整座大楼烧毁
Gonna burn this mother fucker
烧毁...
down, down, down, down, down, down
举起双手
Hands up
音乐一响
when the music drops
双手举高
We both put our hands up
把手放在我的身上
Put your hands on my body
我发誓我曾见过你
Swear I seen you before
我想我记得
I think I remember those
你的眼神
eyes,eyes,eyes(ei...)
宝贝,因为今晚
Cause baby tonight
DJ让我们再次相爱
The DJ got us falling in love again
耶宝贝,今晚
Yeah, baby tonight
DJ让我们再次相爱
The DJ got us falling in love again
那就跳舞,就好像
So dance, dance, like it's the last
今晚是生命中的最后一晚
last night of your life, life
得让你进入正轨
Gonna get you right
宝贝,因为今晚
Cause baby tonight
DJ让我们再次相爱
The DJ got us falling in love again
你知道什么是邪恶的,但从你的眼神和话语中我看不到邪恶
You know evil, speak no evil, see no evil
快来,宝贝,我希望你还能赶上,Go
Get it baby, hope you catch that GO
我们就是如此
That's how we roll
我的生活就像一场电影,而你的像是录影机
My life is a movie and you just TIVO
美女让我像满头辫子一样摇摆
Mami got me switchin like a dreadlock
她不是个摔跤手,但我还是用双腿夹住她的头
She don't wrestle but I got her in a headlock
哦也哦也,让她在床上颤动,她太火太辣了
Yabadabadoo make her bedrock- mami on fire, red hot
badabingbadaboom,世界知名先生走进了房间
badabingbadaboom Mr. Worldwide as I step in the room
宝贝,我可是个赚钱机器
I'm a hustler baby
你知道的,今晚将会是我们两个的世界
But that you knew and tonight it's just me and you
宝贝,因为今晚
Cause baby tonight
DJ让我们再次相爱
The DJ got us falling in love again
耶宝贝,今晚
Yeah, baby tonight
DJ让我们再次相爱
The DJ got us falling in love
那就跳舞,就好像
So dance, dance, like it's the last
今晚是生命中的最后一晚
last night of your life, life
得让你进入正轨
Gonna get you right
宝贝,因为今晚
Cause baby tonight
DJ让我们再次相爱
The DJ got us falling in love again
耶宝贝,今晚
Yeah, baby tonight
DJ让我们再次相爱
The DJ got us falling in love again
那就跳舞,就好像
So dance, dance, like it's the last
今晚是生命中的最后一晚
last night of your life, life
得让你进入正轨
Gonna get you right
宝贝,因为今晚
Cause baby tonight
DJ让我们再次相爱
The DJ got us falling in love again
耶宝贝,今晚
Yeah, thank you DJ haha
我是BOSS制作
谢谢观赏